Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Advertising Vertical Files, 1950-1994 RL.00660
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Advertising Vertical Files
1950-1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00660
54 Linear Feet
32,400 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Advertising Vertical File was transferred to the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in September 1999.
Historical Note
The J. Walter Thompson Company was founded in New York in 1864. The advertising agency's archives document the history, operations, policies, and accomplishments of one of the world's oldest, largest and most innovative advertising firms.
Collection Overview
The Advertising Vertical File contains subject files on a wide range of advertising topics, and is primarily comprised of news clippings, articles, and pamphlets. Topics range from financial information, legal aspects of marketing, employment trends, awards, information on individuals in the industry, media, packaging, trademarks, and marketing research. The file was created and maintained as an internal reference file by the Information Center in JWT's New York Office. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Vertical files; Pamphlets; Advertising agencies -- History; Advertising -- History; Advertising -- Research; J. Walter Thompson Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company
- Accession 1999-0420
  - Advertising (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Advertising (Box 2)
  - Advertising--Bibliography (Box 2)
  - Advertising--Agencies, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings (Box 3)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--Adweek--East Agency Directory (Box 3)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--Adweek--Midwest Agency Directory (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--Adweek--Southeast Agency Directory (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--Adweek--West Agency Directory (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--By Media (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--By Media--Radioand TV (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--By Media-- Newspaper (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Billings--International (Box 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--By Locality (Box 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--By Locality--Chicago (Box 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--By Locality-- New York (Box 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies-- Dictionaries (Box 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Employment (Box 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances (Box 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances--Compensation (Box 6)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances--House (Box 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances--Profit sharing/pension (Box 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances--Rubel Service (Box 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances--Slow Payment (Box 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Finances--Wall Street Transcript (Box 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Forecasts (Box 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--House, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Advertising--Agencies--International, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Management (Box 8)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Management (Box 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Medical (Box 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Organization (Box 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Philosophy (Box 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Relations, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Selection of, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Accounting and Planning (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Fragmentation/Partial Services (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Marketing (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Media (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Size (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Solicitations (Box 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Services and Departments--Specialized (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--A (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Advertising to Women (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ally and Gargano (Carl Ally) (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Altschiller, Reitzfeld, Jackson (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ammirati and Puris (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Angotti, Thomas, Hedge (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Arnell and Bickford (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Arnold and Co. (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ayer, N.W. (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--B (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Backer and Spielvogel (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Backer Spielvogel Bates (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Barickman Advertising (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Barnum Communications (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Bates, Ted (Box 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Batten, Barton, Durstine, and Osborn (Box 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Bayer Bess Vanderwarker (Box 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Beber Silverstein (Box 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Bloom Co. (Box 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Boase Massimi Pollitt (Box 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Bozell and Jacobs (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Brandwynne Associates (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Burnett, Leo Co. (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Burrell Advertising (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Burson Marsteller (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--C (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Cadwell Davis Savage (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Calet, Hirsch, Kurnit and Spector (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Campbell Mithun (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Cargill Wilson Acree (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Carson Roberts (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Chiat/Day (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Chin, Ted and Co. (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Chirburg and Cairns (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Cochrane Chase Livingstone (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Cockfield Brown (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Cohen Pasqualina and Lowe (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Collett Dickenson Pearce (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Compton Advertising (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Conill Advertising Associates (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Crain Communications (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Cramer Krasselt (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies-- Cunningham and Walsh (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--D (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Dancer Fitzgerald Sample (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--D'Arcy Masius Benton and Bowles (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Della Femina (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Dentsu (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Deutsch, David Associates (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Doner, W.B. (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Dorland (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Doyle, Dane, Bernbach (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--DDB Needham (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies-E-H (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Fallon McElligott (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Foot, Cone and Belding (Box 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Foot, Cone and Belding (7 folders) (Box 16)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Freeman, Cliff and Partners (Box 16)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Geer Dubois (Box 17)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Geers Gross (Box 17)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Goodby Berlin Silverstein (Box 17)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Grey Advertising (5 folders) (Box 17)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Griffin Bacal (Box 17)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies- (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--GSD and M (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Havas (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--HBM/Creamer (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Henderson Advertising (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Hill, Holiday (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--I-L (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ingalls Associates (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Interpublic (Box 5B)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Interpublic (4 folders) (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Kelly Nason (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Kenyon and Eckhardt (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ketchum Advertising (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ketchum Macleod and Grove (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Keye/Donna/Pearlstein (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Kirshenbaum and Bond (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Laurence Charles and Free (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Leber and Katz (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Lefton, Al Paul Co. (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Lennen and Newell (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Lintas (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Lois Holland Callaway (Lois Pitts Gershon) (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--M (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Marschalk (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Marsteller (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Martin, J.P. Associates (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--MCA (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--McCaffrey and McCall (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--McCann Erickson (Box 18)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Mickleberry (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Mingo Jones (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--N-P (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Needham, Harper and Steers (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Noble and Associates (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Norton Simon (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ogilvy and Mather (4 folders) (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Ogilvy Group (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Omnicom (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies- (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Omnicom (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Papert Koenig Lois (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Plapler (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--PMS and VW (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Proctor and Gardner (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Publicis (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Q-Z (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Rafshoon (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Rice and Rice (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Richards Group (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Riney, Hal (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Rogers, Peter (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Saatchi and Saatchi (3 folders) (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Scali McCabe Sloves (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Smith Burke and Azzam (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Sosa and Associates (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Tatham Laird and Kudner (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Tatham RSCG (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--TBWA (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Tinker, Jack (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Tucker Wayne (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Uniworld (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Wade Advertising (Box 20)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Wells Rich Greene (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Wieden and Kennedy (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Yardang, Ed and Associates (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Young and Rubicam (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Specific Agencies--Zebra Advertising (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Appropriations (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Appropriations--Industrial (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Advertising--Appropriations--Budget (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Advertising--Art (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Advertising--Awards (including "Badvertising," Andy, Dandy, Echo, and Stephen E. Kellys) (4 folders) (Box 23)
  - Advertising--Awards (including "Badvertising," Andy, Dandy, Echo, and Stephen E. Kellys) (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards-- Adman of the Year (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards--Hall of Fame (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards--Saturday Review (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards--American Business Press (ABP) (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards--Newsmakers (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards--Popai (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Awards--TV (Box 24)
  - Advertising--Biography (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Biography--A-D (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Biography--E-K (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Biography--L-P (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Biography--Q-Z (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Biography--Commercial Directors (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Biography--Women (Box 25)
  - Advertising--Cartoons (Box 26)
  - Advertising--Casting (Box 26)
  - Advertising--Censorship (Box 26)
  - Advertising--Coincidental Similarities (Box 26)
  - Advertising--Color (Box 26)
  - Advertising--Commercials (Box 27)
  - Advertising--Commercials--Jingles (Box 27)
  - Advertising--Commercials--Length (Box 27)
  - Advertising--Commercials--Music (Box 27)
  - Advertising--Commercials--Public Opinion--Video Storybooks (Box 27)
  - Advertising--Commercials--Repetition (Box 28)
  - Advertising--Commercials--Talent (Box 28)
  - Advertising--Commercials--TV, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Advertising--Commercials--TV--Animation (Box 29)
  - Advertising--Commercials--TV--Production (Box 29)
  - Advertising--Commercials--"Zapping" (Box 29)
  - Advertising--Consultants (Box 29)
  - Advertising--Copy, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Advertising--Copy--Price Quoting (Box 30)
  - Advertising--Copy--Tyler (Box 30)
  - Advertising--Copy--Writing (Box 31)
  - Advertising--Costs (Box 31)
  - Advertising--Costs--Trends( JWT), 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Advertising--Criticism, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Advertising--Criticism--PAM (Box 32)
  - Advertising--Criticism--Public Opinions (Box 33)
  - Advertising--Deceptive Ads (Box 33)
  - Advertising--Departments (Box 33)
  - Advertising--Ethics (Box 33)
  - Advertising--Expenditures (Box 33)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--Annual Review (Box 34)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--As % of sales (Box 34)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Associations (Box 34)
  - Ad vertising--Expenditures--Coen estimates (Box 34)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies--Adweek--East Client Budget Directory (Box 35)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies-- Adweek--West Client Budget Directory (Box 35)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies--Top advertised brands (Box 35)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies--Top 100 national advertised--1955-1956 (Box 36)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies--Top 100 national advertised--1957-1958 (Box 36)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies--Top 100 national advertised--1959-1960 (Box 36)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Companies--Top 100 national advertised--1961-1962 (Box 36)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--General, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Agriculture (Box 36)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Alcoholic Beverages (2 folders) (Box 37)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Automobiles (Box 37)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Banking (Box 37)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Banking (Box 38)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Clothing (Box 38)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Drugs and Toiletries (Box 38)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Brand by brand (Box 38)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Top 5 by category (Box 38)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Electronics (Box 38)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Food (Box 39)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Food Service (Box 39)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Insurance (Box 39)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--LNA Leading Advertised brands, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Retail (Box 39)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Soft Drinks (Box 40)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Tobacco products (Box 40)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Toys and games (Box 40)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry-- Transportation (Box 40)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Travel (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Travel-- HKF Travel and Tourism Report (Box 41)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Travel-- Domestic, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Travel--Local (State/Area/Community) (Box 41)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Industry--Travel-- International (Box 41)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media (Box 41)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Business Papers (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Consumer Magazines (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Farm Papers (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media-- Newspapers (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media-- Newspapers-- 1948-1969 (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Newspapers-- 1970-198? (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Outdoor (Box 42)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV (Box 43)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV --Radio-- 1966-1973 (Box 43)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV --Radio-- 1974-1980 (Box 44)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV --Radio-- 1981-1986 (Box 45)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV --Radio--Clippings (Box 45)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV-- Television (Box 46)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV-- Television-- TvBS Spot TV Investment Annual Reports (Box 47)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--by Media--Radio and TV-- Television--International (Box 47)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--International, 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--International-- World Advertising Expenditures (Box 48)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--International--Asia (Box 48)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--International--Canada (Box 48)
  - Advertising--Expenditures--International--Great Britain (Box 48)
  - Advertising--Forecasts (Box 48)
  - Advertising--History (Box 49)
  - Advertising--History--GuinnessAds (Box 49)
  - Advertising--Inquiry (Box 49)
  - Advertising--International, 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Advertising--International--Africa (Box 50)
  - Advertising--International-- Asia (Box 50)
  - Advertising--International-- Japan (Box 51)
  - Advertising--International-- Australia (Box 51)
  - Advertising--International-- Europe (Box 51)
  - Advertising--International-- Europe--France (Box 51)
  - Advertising--International-- Europe--Germany (Box 51)
  - Advertising--International--Europe--Great Britain (Box 51)
  - Advertising--International--Europe--Italy (Box 52)
  - Advertising--International-- Europe--Scandinavia (Box 52)
  - Advertising--International-- Europe--USSR (Box 52)
  - Advertising--International-- Latin America (Box 52)
  - Advertising--International--Middle East (Box 52)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations (Box 53)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--4A (Box 53)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--AAF (Box 53)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Copyright and Reproduction (Box 53)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Endorsements (Box 53)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal (Box 53)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Antitrust and Monopoly (Box 54)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Communications Commission (Box 54)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Trade Commission, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Trade Commission-- FTC News (Box 54)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Trade Commission-- Corrective Advertising (Box 55)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Trade Commission--Hearings Oct. 1971, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Trade Commission--Substantiation (Box 55)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Federal--Federal Trade Commission--Tax Aspects (Box 55)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--International (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Pricing (Box 56)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Self Regulation, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Self Regulation--by Media (Box 57)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Self Regulation--by Media--Code News (Box 57)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Self Regulation--by Media--NAB (Box 57)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Self Regulation--by Media--NAD-NARB, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Self Regulation--by Media--NAD-NARB (Box 58)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries (Box 58)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries--Automobile (Box 58)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries--Drugs (Box 58)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries--Food (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries--Tobacco (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries--Toiletries (Box 59)
  - Advertising--Laws and Regulations--Specific Industries--Toys (Box 59)